A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 7, Accession 7 FA1189
Rockefeller Archive Center
- America-China Society / America-China Forum Programs and Staff, 1986-2002; 13
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, C, 1995-1999 (Box 36, Folder 334)
    Includes snapshots of Chinese gowns from the 1940s, enclosed in letter from Pamela Ki Mai Chen, November 16, 1998.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, C, 1995-1999; Still Images: six color 4"x 6" prints. (Box 36, Folder 334)
    Snapshots of Chinese gowns from the 1940s, enclosed in letter from Pamela Ki Mai Chen, November 16, 1998.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, D, 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 335)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, David Denoon, 1992-1999 (Box 36, Folder 336)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, E, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 337)
    Includes Sir Richard Evans.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, F, 1994-1998 (Box 37, Folder 338)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, G, 1994-1999 (Box 37, Folder 339)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, H, 1993-1999 (Box 37, Folder 340-341)
  - Individual Correspondence, Herbert J. Hansell, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 342-344)
  - Individual Correspondence, John Holden, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 345)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, I-J, 1995-19981 (Box 38, Folder 346)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, K, 1994-1998 (Box 38, Folder 347)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, L, 1993-1999 (Box 38, Folder 348-349)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Nicholas Lardy, 1992-1999 (Box 38, Folder 350-351)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Herbert Levin, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 352)
    Announcement letters concerning Levin's new position with the ACS.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Herbert Levin, 1994-1996, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 353)
    Personal and professional correspondence. Includes letters announcing his new position with the ACS, resumes, and correspondence concerning the ACS's merger with the NCUSCR.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Herbert Levin (Foreign Affairs Oral History), 1994 (Box 39, Folder 354)
    Transcript of Herbert Levin's interview for the Foreign Affairs Oral History Program at Georgetown University, concerning his work in Foreign Service from 1956 - 1991.
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, M, 1993-1998 (Box 39, Folder 355)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, N, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 356)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, O, 1992-1998 (Box 39, Folder 357)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Michel Oksenberg, 1987-1998 (Box 39, Folder 358)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, P, 1994-1998 (Box 39, Folder 359-360)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, R, 1993-1999 (Box 40, Folder 361)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, J. Stapleton Roy, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 362)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, S, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 363-365)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Peter Yoshiyasu Sato, 1995-1999 (Box 40, Folder 366)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Robert A. Scalapino, 1994-1998 (Box 40, Folder 367)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, T, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 368)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, U - V, 1994-1999 (Box 41, Folder 369)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, W, 1994-1999 (Box 41, Folder 370-371)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, X - Y, 1995-1999 (Box 41, Folder 372)
  - Individual Correspondence and Contacts, Z, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 373)
  - Huang Hua, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 374)
    Includes references to Huang Hua Retrospective Project on Sino - U. S. Relations.
  - Ji Chaozhu, 1992-1997 (Box 41, Folder 375)
  - Li Daoyu, 1993-1998 (Box 41, Folder 376)
  - America - China Society: Establishment, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 377)
    Includes National Committee memo concerning implications of new ACS organization for NCUSCR programs and perception.
  - America-China Society: Information Sheet and Brochure, 1991, undated (Box 41, Folder 378)
    Sample brochure, 1991, and ACS statement of purpose.
  - America - China Society: Documentation, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 379)
    Copies for the NCUSCR of the ACS's Certificate of Incorporation, Bylaws, Tax Determination Letter, 1987-1992.
  - America - China Society: Tax Status, 1989, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 380)
  - America - China Society: Employee Confidentiality Agreement, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 381)
  - America - China Society: Executive Director Candidates, 1987, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 382)
    Candidate resumes and correspondence.
  - America - China Society Staff: Interview Candidates, 1994-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 383)
    Resumes and inquiries, particularly for program associate position.
  - America - China Society: Internship, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 384)
    Resumes of intern candidates from master's program at Columbia University School of International and Public Affairs.
  - America - China Society: Office Correspondence (General), 1993-1999 (Box 42, Folder 385)
    Announcements and job openings relating to China. Press Requests
  - America - China Society: Office Correspondence (Merger with NCUSCR), 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 386)
    Correspondence concerning ACS governance and fundraising. audits, and other details of the transition to the NCUSCR.
  - America - China Society: Holiday Cards Received, 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 387)
    Christmas and New Years. includes replies.
  - America - China Society: Office Lease (350 Park Ave), 1996-1999 (Box 42, Folder 388)
  - America - China Society: Office Lease Discussion, 1999 -2000 (Box 42, Folder 389)
    Concerning termination of lease at 350 Park Avenue upon the ACS's merger with the NCUSCR.
  - America - China Society: Office Renovations (350 Park Ave), 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 390)
    Brookbridge Consulting Services.
  - America - China Society: Office Renovations (350 Park Ave), 1996-1998; Oversized diazo whiteprint, circa 24" x 36". (Drawer F 7, Folder 1)
    Construction Plan, 350 Park Avenue, 4th Floor. Brookbridge Consulting Services, Inc., 1996 June 4.
    General
    Separated from Series 13, Box 42, folder 390.
  - Kissinger Associates (General), 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 391)
    File concerns payment and reimbursement of Century Association bills for costs of ACS board meetings, Feburary 10, 1998, and January 26, 1999.
  - Kissinger Associates Staff: General, 1995-1998 (Box 42, Folder 392)
    Penny Rose and Theresa Cimino. Lists of Chinese leaders, and miscellaneous scheduling.
  - Kissinger Associates Staff: L. Paul (Jerry) Bremmer, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 393)
  - Kissinger Associates Staff: Suzanne McFarlane and Donna Freet (Henry Kissinger's Office), 1996-1999 (Box 43, Folder 394)
  - Kissinger Associates Staff: Shan Mei, 1996-1999 (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - America - China Society: Reference Files, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 396)
    List of Organizations Involved in Asian Affairs, 1994 July. list of Leaders of the People's Republic of China, 1995 March. Map of the People's Republic of China (Cartographic Publishing House), June 1981 (oversized).
  - America - China Society: Reference Files, 1994-1995; Oversized, printed color map, circa 21"x 30". (Drawer F 7, Folder 1)
    Map of the People's Republic of China (Cartographic Publishing House, June 1981).
    Separated from Series 13, Box 43, folder 396.
  - Office News Clippings, 1995-1999 (Box 43, Folder 397)
  - News Clippings and Internet Articles, 1997-1999 (Box 43, Folder 398-399)
  - Henry Kissinger Articles, 1993-1998 (Box 43, Folder 400)
  - Herbert Levin Informational Memos to Cyrus R. Vance, 1995-1999 (Box 43, Folder 401)
  - Herbert Levin Biography, circa 1994 (Box 43, Folder 402)
  - Speeches and Speech Materials, 1995-1999 (Box 43, Folder 403-404)
    Reference file of speeches, 1995-1996, and Herbert Levin speech materials.
  - Taiwan, 1995-1997 (Box 44, Folder 405)
  - Briefing Book on Japan, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 406)
  - Taiwan Briefing Book, 1999 December (Box 44, Folder 407)
    Additional background materials for the meeting with representatives of the Taiwan Presidential Candidates, Palo Alto, CA, 1999 December 6-7.
  - United States - China Dialogue (Briefing Book), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 408)
    Readings collected for Tenth U. S. - China Dialogue, Beijing, 2000 January.
  - Vice Premier Tian Jiyun Dinner, 1988 May 12 (Box 44, Folder 409)
    River Club. File consists only of list of American participants for the July 1988 Conference in Beijing.
  - U. S. - China Economic Symposium (Planning Notebook), 1988 July 15-17 (Box 44, Folder 410)
    Beijing. Mary Wadsworth-Darby planning notebook and notes.
  - America - China Society Conference (Transcripts), 1989 May (Box 44, Folder 411)
    Conference on "China, the U. S., and the Future of Asia," May 23-24. See also box 34, folders 300-302.
  - America - China Society Meeting with Huang Hua Delegation (Transcript), 1991 January 15 (Box 44, Folder 412)
    Edited transcript of meeting at the Metropolitan Museum of Art. See also transcript in Box 34, folder 310.
  - Shanghai Communique Commemoration: Dinner, Planning, and Letters of Appreciation, 1992 April 29 (Box 44, Folder 413)
  - Shanghai Mayor Huang Ju Delegation, 1992 April 27 - May 5 (Box 44, Folder 414)
    New York, Washington, DC, and San Francisco. Visit coincided with the Twentieth Anniversary Commemoration of the Shanghai Communique.
  - Chinese Visits to U. S. and Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 415)
    Mary Wadsworth-Darby correspondence and memos to Henry Kissinger and others. Henry Kissinger and Herbert Levin Meetings with Chinese.
  - China Society for Strategy and Management Research (CSSM) Delegation, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 416)
    Proposals and planning for a Symposium on U. S. - China Relations and Economic Cooperation. scheduled for 1995 March 13, but then postponed.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: General, 1995 July 1-5 (Box 45, Folder 417)
    Itinerary, biographies, readings, correspondence and planning.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: General, 1995 July 1-5; Still Images: Color prints, consisting of 3 snapshots (3.5 x 5.5) and 2 group photos (5.25 x 8). (Box 45, Folder 417)
    Three snapshots of delegation in China; group photo of Henry Kissinger visit to Nankai University, Tianjen; and group photo (with identifications) of the delegation with Premier Li Peng.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: Briefing (Washington, DC), 1995 June 5 (Box 45, Folder 418)
    State Department Briefing.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: Briefing Materials, 1995 June 5 (Box 45, Folder 419)
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: Herbert Levin File, 1995 July 1-5 (Box 45, Folder 420)
    Includes Notes on Meetings, July 3-4. correspondence and planning.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: Correspondence, 1995 July 1-5 (Box 45, Folder 421)
    Faxes between Herbert Levin, Nancy Grunthal, Donna Dayton.
  - America - China Society Beijing Trip: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1995 July 1-5 (Box 45, Folder 422)
    Henry Kissinger and Herbert Levin thank you letters. Letter to all attendees and directors with Kissinger clipping (not enclosed), July 24-25.
  - President Jiang Zemin Luncheon, 1995 October 23 (Box 46, Folder 423-424)
    Waldorf Astoria, New York. Jointly sponsored by the ACS, Asia Society, Council on Foreign Relations, Foreign Policy Association, NCUSCR, and United States - China Business Council. Correspondence among sponsors, organization and planning, ACS invitations, Protocol List, Thank Yous.
  - President Jiang Zemin Luncheon, 1995 October 23; Still Image: Five black-and-white contact sheet prints. (Box 46, Folder 423-424)
    Photographs from the luncheon, by Elsa Ruiz.
  - Henry A. Kissinger Address, 1996 March 25 (Box 46, Folder 425)
    Address on the "Future of United States - China Relations," Century Association, NY. Twenty-Fifth anniversary of beginnings of Ping Pong Diplomacy and Kissinger's secret visit to China.
  - Delegation from China (Postponed), 1996 June 19 (Box 46, Folder 426)
    Delegation invited from the PRC for a visit reciprocating the ACS's Beijing Trip in July 1995. Trip postponed.
  - Minister of Defense Chi Haotian Dinner, 1996 December 6 (Box 46, Folder 427-428)
    Cosponsored with the NCUSCR. Correspondence and Planning.
  - Shanghai Communique‚ Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1997 February 20 (Box 46, Folder 429-430)
    Program planning and correspondence, invitations, speakers, press, thank yous.
  - Shanghai Communique‚ Twenty-Fifth Anniversary (Meeting Transcript), 1997 February 20 (Box 46, Folder 431)
    Transcript of taped program (2 tapes).
  - China People's Assocation for Friendship with Foreign Countries Delegation Luncheon, 1997 April 14 (Box 47, Folder 432)
    Private luncheon hosted by ACS. Also includes discussion of possible ACS trip to China in 1997.
  - Ping Pong Diplomacy Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Commemoration (Beijing), 1997 August 6-10 (Box 47, Folder 433)
    Herbert Levin attended on behalf of the ACS.
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon: General, 1997 October 30 (Box 47, Folder 434)
    ANA Hotel, Washington, DC. Namelists, Jiang Zemin speech, Planning Meetings.
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon: General, 1997 October 30; Still Images: 12 black-and-white 8"x 10" contact sheets, plus partial strips of images. (Box 47, Folder 434)
    Event photos.
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon: Planning and Arrangements, 1997 October 30 (Box 47, Folder 435)
    Includes schedules, draft remarks for Barber Conable and Henry Kissinger, seating arrangements, Bios, and Payments and Accounting.
  - Jiang Zemin Visit: Press Coverage, 1997 October-November (Box 47, Folder 436)
    Includes Jiang Zemin's speech at Harvard University, November 1.
  - Qian Qichen Visit, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 437)
    Invitation to Foreign Minister Qian Qichen to meet with the ACS when he visited in the fall.
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: General, 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 47, Folder 438-439)
    Schedule, Invitations and Menus. Bios. copies of Relevant Faxes from 1995 Beijing Trip. chart of "Key Economic Decisionmaking Bodies" in China. Ambassador Sakutaro Tanino Dinner Invitation (August 31). Correspondence with the American Embassy in Beijing. Guests. Thank Yous. Guest Expense Reimbursement.
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Notes, 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 47, Folder 440)
    Notes on planning and program discussions by Herbert Levin and others.
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Correspondence with Henry Kissinger, 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 48, Folder 441)
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Correspondence with Beijing, 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 48, Folder 442)
    Correspondence mainly with Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs.
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Correspondence with Directors (Attendees), 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 48, Folder 443-444)
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Correspondence with the PRC Embassy in the U. S., 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 48, Folder 445)
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Press Coverage, 1998 August 31 - September 4 (Box 48, Folder 446)
  - ACS Trip to Beijing: Photographs, 1998 August 31 - September 4; Still Images: 2 group photos (and duplicates; approx. 6"x 8"); 26 informal photos (also 6"x 8"; number includes duplicates), and 15 snapshots (mainly 4"x6"). (Box 48, Folder 447)
    Color prints: 2 group photos with identifications, plus 22 informal photos and 15 snapshots. Includes some duplicates. File includes one cover letter.
  - Twentieth Anniversary of the Normalization of U. S. - China Relations Commemoration: General, 1998 December 15 (Box 48, Folder 448)
    Event File ("Carried to Event"). Speaker Scenario and Program. Directors' Responses. Earlier Event Planning Information. Press. Private Reception. Thank Yous.
  - Twentieth Anniversary of the Normalization of U. S. - China Relations Commemoration: Correspondence with NCUSCR and Council on Foreign Relations, 1998 December 15 (Box 48, Folder 449)
  - Twentieth Anniversary of the Normalization of U. S. - China Relations Commemoration: Correspondence with Henry A. Kissinger and Cyrus R. Vance, 1998 December 15 (Box 48, Folder 450)
  - Twentieth Anniversary of the Normalization of U. S. - China Relations Commemoration: Speaker Invitations, 1998 December 15 (Box 49, Folder 451)
    Invitations and responses. Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale, Richard Holbrooke, Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, Winston Lord, Thomas R. Pickering, Stanley Roth, Leonard Woodcock. Winston Lord delivered Leonard Woodcock's remarks.
  - Twentieth Anniversary of the Normalization of U. S. - China Relations Commemoration: Financial Accounting and Reimbursements, 1998 December 15 (Box 49, Folder 452)
    Includes Waldorf Astoria arrangements.
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: Planning and Arrangements, 1999 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 453)
    Includes schedules, seating charts, financial accounting and reimbursements.
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: Correspondence with Kissinger, PRC Embassy, and U. S. State Department, 1999 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 454)
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: Correspondence with Other Organizations, 1999 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 455)
    In addition to the NCUSCR and the ACS, cosponsoring organizations included the Asia Society, the Committee of 100, the Council on Foreign Relations, the U. S. - China Policy Foundation, and the U. S. Chamber of Commerce.
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: Correspondence with Directors, 1999 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 456)
    Includes responses to event invitation.
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: NCUSCR Planning and Arrangements, 1999 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 457)
    NCUSCR correspondence with the Chinese Embassy and the Hotel concerning dinner arrangements.
  - Zhu Rongji Dinner: Photographs, 1999 April 9; Still Images: 7 color contact sheets (8.5"x 11"). (Box 49, Folder 458)
    Seven contact sheets with color images of the event. Photographs copyright U. S. Chamber of Commerce. T. Michael Keza, chief photographer.
  - Possible Delegation from China, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 459)
  - Resumes of PRC Leaders, 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 460)
    Miscellaneous file contains resumes for members of the Huang Hua Delegation, 1991. plus lists and correspondence, and statements by Wang Jisi.
  - Correspondence with Chinese Embassy (Washington, DC), 1993-1995, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 461)
    Mainly fax correspondence with Yang Jiechi and Xu Shangwei from Mary Wadsworth-Darby and Herbert Levin.
  - Minister of Defense Chi Haotian Visit: Invitation and Background, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 462)
    Correspondence originally filed in folder labeled "Resumes of PRC Leaders."
  - Background Readings on China, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 463)
    Includes reference information on living standards in Shanghai, 1999.
  - America - China Society: Office Move and Merger with NCUSCR, 1999 August-September; Still Image: Polaroid images of furniture and file cabinets attached to 8.5"x 11" sheets of paper> (Box 50, Folder 464)
    Office equipment and furniture. communications, accounting, and file management details.
  - David M. Albert (Personal), 1998-1999 (Box 50, Folder 465)
    Resume and letters of reference.
  - David M. Albert (Personal), 1999; Still Images: Two 5.5"x 8" color prints. (Box 50, Folder 465)
    Group photo from ACS Trip to Beijing, 1998, and one unidentified group photo.
  - David M. Albert Outgoing Correspondence, 1999 September - 2000 May (Box 50, Folder 466)
  - America - China Society Ideas File, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 467)
    Miscellaneous program and mailing list ideas.
  - History and Chronology of U. S. - China Relations (Reference File), 1965-1993 (Box 50, Folder 468)
    Includes synopses prepared by Noah Kupferman in 1993 on topics of "Sino - U. S. Normalization Negotiations under Carter" and "Sino - U. S. Rapprochement: The Nixon - Kissinger Years."
  - America - China Society Founding and Early History, 1986-1992 (Box 50, Folder 469-470)
  - Shanghai Communique Anniversary Commemorations: Letters from U. S. Presidents, 1992, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 471)
    Letters of greeting from Richard Nixon and Jimmy Carter, April 1992, and from George H. W. Bush, April 1992 and February 1997.
  - America - China Society Board: General Administration, 1994-2000 (Box 50, Folder 472)
    ACS Statement of Purpose, Financial Position, 1999, Expense Policy, Fellows List, Forms of Address for ACS Directors.
  - America-China Society Board: Membership Invitations, 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 473)
  - America - China Society Directors: Biographies, circa 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 474)
  - Directors Correspondence, Madeleine K. Albright, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 475)
  - Directors Correspondence, Robert Allen (AT&T), 1992-1998 (Box 51, Folder 476)
  - Directors Correspondence, Baker - Blumenthal, 1989-2001 (Box 51, Folder 477)
    James A. Baker III, Charlene Barshefsky, Samuel R. Berger, Shirley Temple Black, Michael Blumenthal.
  - Directors Correspondence, Zbigniew Brzezinski, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 478)
    Resignation letter.
  - Directors Correspondence, McGeorge Bundy, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 479)
    Resignation.
  - Directors Correspondence, George H. W. Bush, 1993-1998 (Box 51, Folder 480)
  - Directors Correspondence, Carter - Clinton, 1990-2002 (Box 51, Folder 481)
    President Jimmy Carter, Warren Christopher, President William J. Clinton.
  - Directors Correspondence, L. M. Cook (ARCO), 1987-1994 (Box 51, Folder 482)
  - Directors Correspondence, Kenneth Dam, 1989-2000 (Box 51, Folder 483)
    Includes correspondence relating to contributions from IBM.
  - Directors Correspondence, Robert Daniell (United Technologies), 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 484)
  - Directors Correspondence, Lawrence S. Eagleburger, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 485)
  - Directors Correspondence, James E. Fligg (Amoco/BP Amoco), 1995-1999 (Box 51, Folder 486)
  - Directors Correspondence, Thomas S. Foley, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 487)
  - Directors Correspondence, Gerald R. Ford, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 488)
  - Directors Correspondence, Cyrus F. Freidheim Jr. (Booz, Allen and Hamilton), 1990-1999 (Box 51, Folder 489)
    Includes his notes on ACS trips to China in 1991 and 1993. Paul Fribourg and Donald Staheli (Continental Grain Company).
  - Directors Correspondence, Paul Fribourg and Donald Staheli (Continental Grain Company), 1995-1999 (Box 51, Folder 490)
  - Directors Correspondence, Louis Gerstner (IBM), 1989-2000 (Box 52, Folder 491)
    Also includes correspondence pertaining to contributions from RJR Nabisco (of which Gerstner was chair, prior to his employment with IBM).
  - Directors Correspondence, Golub - Gray, 1989-2000 (Box 52, Folder 492)
    Harvey Golub (American Express), Hanna Holborn Gray, 1989, 1995.
  - Directors Correspondence, Maurice Greenberg (AIG) and T. C. Hsu (Starr Foundation), 1989-2000 (Box 52, Folder 493)
  - Directors Correspondence, Alexander Haig, Jr. and Sherwood Goldberg, 1993-1999 (Box 52, Folder 494)
  - Directors Correspondence, Herbert J. Hansell, 1986-1994 (Box 52, Folder 495-497)
  - Directors Correspondence, Herbert J. Hansell, 1995-2000 (Box 53, Folder 498-500)
  - Directors Correspondence, Carla A. Hills, 1994-1997 (Box 53, Folder 501)
  - Directors Correspondence, Arthur W. Hummel, Jr., 1993-2000 (Box 53, Folder 502)
  - Directors Correspondence, Henry A. Kissinger, 1989-2001 (Box 53, Folder 503)
  - Directors Correspondence, Thomas G. Labrecque (Chase), 1990-1999 (Box 53, Folder 504)
  - Directors Correspondence, Lake - Levin, 1997-2000 (Box 53, Folder 505)
    Anthony Lake, 1997-1998, Herbert Levin, 2000, Winston Lord, 1997-1999.
  - Directors Correspondence, Lorch - Lord, 1994-1999 (Box 53, Folder 506)
    George A. Lorch, 1994-1997, Winston Lord, 1997-1999.
  - Directors Correspondence, Masin - McFarlane, 1994-1998 (Box 53, Folder 507)
    Michael T. Masin (GTE), 1995-1998, Robert McFarlane,1994-1995, 1998.